Null Atwood

Summary

Software engineer with experience coding in a variety of different languages, and education focused on artificial intelligence. Fast learner who strives to continuously improve at their job and contribute to a positive workplace environment.

Skills

Programming – Experienced writing viable, clean code in languages including C, C++, Python, JavaScript, MIPS, x86 Assembly, and Rust.

Software Engineering – Able to solicit and codify functional and non-functional system requirements, develop system architecture, and design/implement unit and systems tests to ensure compliance with system requirements.

Product Delivery – Worked in a team on a capstone project and successfully delivered MVP for the Patient Monitoring Robot, sponsored by Intel, which was recognised with an award at the Oregon State University 2023 Engineering Expo.

Communication – Effectively and respectfully communicates with coworkers, management, and clients. Experienced in writing semi-daily reports for management and daily reports for clientele as an ADP staff member, and in verbal communication as a restaurant server.

Work Experience

Delivery Associate at Rafter D in Salem, OR | 2023.11-Present (6 months)

Inspect and load cargo van in morning, deliver packages according to customer instructions and best practices, inspect van again after returning to station.

Warehouse Worker at Target DC in Albany, OR | 2023.08 – 2023.09 (1 month) Load product into trailers, both by hand and using manual or electric pallet jacks. Resigned due to preexisting injury making nature of work unsafe.

Dishwasher at Cornbread Café in Eugene, OR | 2023.07 – 2023.08 (1 month) Wash, sanitise, and transport dishes and cookware, prioritising based on needs of other departments. Laid off due to permanent closure.

Self-Employed Delivery Driver \mid 2019.10 – 2023.11 (4 year, 1 month span with gaps for education) Accept and complete food and parcel delivery contracts offered by various companies including Amazon and Uber, in a timely manner and in accordance with any delivery and pickup instructions.

Restaurant Server at Go Vegan in Antioch, CA | 2019.01 – 2019.07 (6 months)

Seat guests, take orders, prepare drinks, serve food, bus tables, take phone calls, and otherwise maintain front of house. Was required to memorise full menu (over 100 items) and was trusted to help with new server training. Resigned due to planned move to Oregon.

All Day Play Staff at Wag Hotels in San Francisco, CA | 2015.09 – 2016.07, 2017.12 (10 months) Supervise large groups of dogs (up to 50 large or 100 small during holidays), preventing scuffles and maintaining cleanliness. Write daily reports for clients and semi-daily reports for management. Port dogs

between hotel areas. Assist guest services when finished with own duties ahead of time. Was recognised as employee of the month in January 2016 and was one of a few employees selected for the experimental Puppy All Day Play programme. Resigned to focus on education.

Sales Floor Team Member at Target in Antioch, CA | 2015.05 – 2015.09 Stock shelves, zone, reshop, and assist guests. Cashiered as needed during busy hours and was often requested as first choice for this assistance. Resigned to begin working at Wag Hotels.

Education

Oregon State University, 2020-2023

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science with Artificial Intelligence Option Currently enrolled in final course required for degree and on track for graduation in June. Course is asynchronous and I am able and willing to commit to full-time work before graduation. 3.71 institutional GPA, 3.74 cumulative GPA